ADRIENNE LEE

SENIOR WEB SPECIALIST

adriennelee.dev adrienneklee@gmail.com Hamilton, ON







PERSONAL PROFILE

As a Senior Web Specialist for Point Blank Creative, I lead the planning, development, and deployment of high-impact web projects, bridging the gap between strategic vision and technical execution. My passion for tech is bolstered by 10+ years experience in Corporate Social Responsibility and has fuelled me in developing accessible, meaningful and responsive web applications.

WEB DEV SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3/SCSS
- Javascript
- ¡Query
- React
- Ruby on Rails
- PHP

- Firebase
- WordPress
- Paired/Group Programming
- Accessibility Standards
- Google Analytics

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology

Web Development Immersive Oct 2021 - December 2021 Intermediate Javascript Intro to Web Development

Toronto Metropolitan University

Masters of Environmental Applied Science and Management

Sept 2009 - May 2011

McMaster University

Bachelors of Biochemistry and Biomedical Science

Sept 2004 - May 2007

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR WEB SPECIALIST

Point Blank Creative (Mar 2023 - Present)

- Leads planning, development, and deployment of complex web projects, ensuring on-time delivery of scalable, accessible, and user-friendly digital products.
- Acts as the primary point of contact with external developers, vendors, and agencies, managing timelines, deliverables, and quality assurance.
- Writes detailed web briefs and functional/technical requirement documents, bridging communication between stakeholders and developers. Maintains technical documentation for the company.
- Provides strategic and technical insight into digital solution design, architecture decisions, and web best practices across multiple platforms.
- Consults on major proposals and sales opportunities, offering guidance on product feasibility, timelines, resources, and budgets.
- Leads key development deliverables, from wireframes and component architecture to QA and launch, aligning closely with accessibility and usability standards.

WEB DEVELOPER

Point Blank Creative (Jan 2022 - Promoted in Role)

- Served as the sole in-house developer, leading the development of responsive, accessible, and user-friendly frontend products that align with strategic campaign goals.
- Developed and maintained scalable interfaces using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, React, and Ruby on Rails.
- Integrated third-party platforms and tools (e.g., Google Analytics, Zapier, Action Network) and customized CMS platforms (WordPress, NationBuilder) to support seamless workflows, project-scalability and client-readiness.
- Created and maintained developer documentation to improve internal knowledge-sharing and onboarding.
- · Advocated for accessibility best practices, ensuring all web experiences meet or exceed WCAG standards.
- Career change featured in: The Globe and Mail

DIRECTOR OF GLOBAL IMPACT

Tourism Cares (Sept 2018 - Oct 2021)

- Managed 160+ external partnerships with travel & tech brands corporate social responsibility, sustainability and DEI strategies.
- Speaker: NY Time Travel Show 2020, TravelCon Boston.
- DEI leadership featured in: The Washington Post

DIRECTOR OF DEVELOPMENT

G Adventures | Planeterra (July 2012 - Sept 2018)

- Worked cross-functionally with Software team to develop mobile fundraising app for consumer audience.
- Oversaw \$1.5M budget and planning process, increased donor revenue by 19% in one calendar year.
- Managed and mentored a globally-dispersed team of 4.